dare2compete.com 2015-06-11

# Privacy Policy | Dare2Compete

#### Privacy Policy

At Dare2Compete.com we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to the use of website, contents and all of the services offered by Dare2Compete.com. In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post supplementary privacy notices to describe how particular services process personal information, which can be found along with the particular services

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website at the below mentioned address or write to us at help@Dare2Compete.com

#### Scope

This statement applies to Dare2Compete’s contents, services and websites.

  * Dare2Compete collects personal information when you register for a Dare2Compete service or otherwise voluntarily provide such information. We may combine personal information collected from you with information from other Dare2Compete services or third parties to provide a better user experience, including customizing content for you. 
  * Dare2Compete uses cookies and other technologies to enhance your online experience and to learn about how you use Dare2Compete services in order to improve the quality of our services. 
  * Dare2Compete’s servers automatically record information when you visit our website or use some of our products, including the URL, IP address, browser type and language, and the date and time of your request. 

The Privacy Policy does not apply to practices of companies Flive (Dare2Compete) do not own or control, or to the people that Flive (Dare2Compete) does not employ or manage.

#### Information collection and use

We offer a number of services that require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

Dare2Compete site collects personally identifiable information (such as your name, email address and an account password) when you register for Dare2Compete site account or when you use certain products or services provided by Dare2Compete site. For use of some specific services, providing some specific personally identifiable information shall be compulsory/ mandatory.

We also offer some of our services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to Dare2Compete in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. 

Dare2Compete may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising.

This Privacy Policy applies to Dare2Compete contents and services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Dare2Compete also automatically receives and records information on shared server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested.

In addition, when you use Dare2Compete site services, you may make some of your personal information public. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return and Dare2Compete site will not be responsible for the use or misuse of such information.

Email communication that you send us via the email links on the Site may be shared with company representatives, partners or employees. From time to time, we may send you service-related emails, such as a welcome email when you come in touch with the Site.

**We use your email address to send you:**

  * Password reminder and registration confirmation 
  * Special offers 
  * News letters 
  * Changes in the service's policy or terms of use 
  * Event based communications such as new event information, invites, reminders etc. 

**Note:** We send users newsletters and updates upon registration. We send newsletters and/or promotional emails on behalf of our alliance partners. As regards special offers, news letters, new event information, invites and reminders, you shall have the option to unsubscribe the same at our website.

**We use your personal information to:**

  * help us provide personalized features 
  * tailor our sites to your interest 
  * to get in touch with you in the case of password retrieval and policy changes 
  * to provide the services requested by you 
  * to preserve social history as governed by existing law or policy 

**We use contact information internally to:**

  * direct our efforts for product improvement 
  * contact you as a survey respondent 
  * notify you if you win any contest; 
  * send you promotional materials from our contest sponsors or advertisers

#### Your choices

  * We offer you choices when we ask for personal information, whenever reasonably possible. 
  * You may decline to provide personal information to us and/or refuse cookies in your browser, although some of our features or services may not function properly as a result. 
  * We make good faith efforts to provide you access to your personal information upon request and to let you correct such data if it is inaccurate and delete it, when reasonably possible. 

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Dare2Compete site will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.

**Dare2Compete will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:**

  * We have your consent to share the information;
  * We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
  * We need to share the information with certain service partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve service issues. (Unless we tell you differently, these partners have no independent right to use this information except to respond to your comments or to resolve the service issues.);
  * We respond to requests from any Indian or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
  * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Dare2Compete [terms of service](http://in.docs.yahoo.com/info/terms/) or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.

#### Cookies

Dare2compet may set and access Dare2Compete cookies on your computer and you may not be able to disable these cookies. Dare2Compete ensures that all information collected and accessed by Dare2Compete through the access of these cookies will be maintained in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Dare2Compete site allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. 

#### Links

Dare2Compete.com may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of customized content and advertising..

#### Affiliated Sites 

Dare2Compete.com may offer some services in connection with other web sites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.

#### Security

Your Dare2Compete account information is password-protected for your privacy and security.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Dare2Compete site may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. . We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.

#### Data integrity

Dare2Compete processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.
